Bryan Crowder

Software Engineer Intern

Bryan Crowder 111 W 7th S Apt 802 Rexburg, Idaho 83440 (541) 310-7024 3107024@gmail.com January 30th, 2019

Dear Employer

I'm currently seeking a Software Engineering internship with you. I believe I would be a strong asset to you and your company not only with my skills but with my work ethic. I bring not only SQL skills but HTML, CSS, MySQL, Linux Operating Systems, JavaScript and I've done work inside of Oracle database learning from a past oracle senior director in databases. I'm currently a student at Brigham Young University Idaho, studying Computer Information Technologies.

I've worked hard every day of my life to get me to where I am today, and I will bring that same competitive work ethic to always be pushing to the next project and the next objective to help with efficiency. If I don't do something right the first time, I always accept responsibility and will learn from my mistakes and will always try to make it right.

In my current position as a Sales Representative I have encountered all types of people and have learned to work with everyone. I have recorded record high sales but along with that, I've helped multiple people leave with a smile on their face because I've helped them understand a current problem while either fixing it or showing them how to fix it to allow them to become self-sufficient.

I feel like I would be a perfect fit for you with my current work experience and knowledge of things I have learned at my current university.

I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely,

Bryan Crowder

Bryan Crowder

111 West 7th South Apt: 802 Rexburg, ID 83440 (541) 310-7024 3107024@gmail.com

SUMMARY

With an extensive knowledge in programming and hard work ethic, I help almost any team become better. I have a background in Sales which allows me to be relatable to people while making sure that I get things done right the first time. I have worked 30+hours while being a full-time student for a year and have averaged a 3.6 GPA, showing how hard I can work with my allotted time.

EXPERIENCE

AT&T Authorized Retailer, Rexburg ID— Sales Associate

March 2018- Current

On a daily basis I would have to organize, clean and barcode multiple storage bins and rebuild machinery while being able to moves stuff with a forklift.

Smith Frozen Foods, Weston OR — *Forklift Operator*

July 2017 - January 2018

On a daily basis I would have to organize, clean and barcode multiple storage bins and rebuild machinery while being able to moves stuff with a forklift.

Smith Frozen Foods, Weston OR — *HR Representative*

June 2014 - December 2016

I worked in Human Resources helping many employees and other outside people to get in contact with the staff, along with resolving conflicts and being a representative of the company.

EDUCATION

Brigham Young University Idaho, Rexburg, ID — *GPA: 3.6 Computer courses GPA: 3.85*

January 2017 - Current

I'm currently a student, studying a bachelor's in computer information technologies with a cluster in Business.

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Java

SQL

MYSQL

Oracle/DB

AWARDS

Eagle Scout

Regional champion of Future Business Leaders of America in Business Law and economics

LANGUAGES

English

VOLUNTEER WORK

I served as a service missionary for my church for 9 months in London, England. I had dedicated 2 year of my life for my church but then was later diagnosed with Crohn's Disease, making it so I was unable to finish those 2 years.